Polycast 是面向那些对 Polymer 的 web 组件感兴趣的人
Polycast is for anybody who's really into web components in Polymer.
如果你是个新手
If you're an absolute beginner, you
还没有接触过这些东西  我会
haven't worked with these things before, I'm
给你一些便于你入门的材料  给你演示
going to give you some getting started material, show you how
如何操作一些组件
to work with a few components.
如果你是有一定经验的开发者
If you're a more advanced developer,
我有一些小贴士和技巧
I actually have some tips and tricks
以及其它一些很酷的东西  都是 Polymer 团队独家的哦
and other cool stuff that's coming exclusive from the Polymer teams.
那你几乎可以比外面的任何人都
So you get to hear about it before pretty much anybody else
提早知道
in the outside world.
我们用了一些神奇的东西
We've got a little bit of Hollywood magic
来应用到节目里
that we've incorporated into the show
我可以在屏幕上画画
so that I can draw on the screen,
我可以指出代码的细节
I can point out the particulars of the code,
而且我可以带你们一起进入文本编辑器
and I can actually bring you inside the text editor with me.
这样的感觉更像是我们在一起创建组件
So it can feel more like we're building a component together,
而不是你干坐在那看视频
and not like you're just sitting there watching some video.
Polycast 在 Google Developers Youtude 频道上
Polycast comes out on the Google Developers YouTube
每两周发布一次视频
channel every two weeks.
你可以订阅那个频道
So you can subscribe to that channel.
那样的话你就一集也不会错过了  很棒吧
And that way, you will never miss an episode, which is pretty awesome.
你也可以在我们的频道上查看播放列表
You can also go find our playlist on the channel.
你可以标记书签  而且你可以看到所有原先的记录
You can bookmark that, and you can see the entire back catalog.
我想跟所有在观看视频的开发者说的是
One thing I would say to any developer watching
如果你真的喜欢这个节目
is that if you really like the show,
别忘了在 Youtube 视频下评论
leave me a comment down there on YouTube.
我会阅读所有的评论
I read all of the comments.
而且会尽量回复
I try to respond to as many as I possibly can.
当你问了很有价值的问题时
And when you leave a really good question,
我们可以在未来的节目中提出
we can highlight it in future episodes.
今天在 Polycast 我要向你们展示一个很重要的技巧
Today on Polycast, I'm going to show you a very important trick.
现在我们开始吧
So let's dive in.
[MUSIC PLAYING]